{
  "staff": [
    {
      "username": "admin",
      "password": "admin",
      "id": "f18e"
    },
    {
      "username": "test",
      "password": "test",
      "id": "f532"
    }
  ],
  "assignments": [
    {
      "id": "f9c5",
      "AssignmentTitle": "asdfasdasdffasd",
      "questions": [
        {
          "qTitl": "asdfdsasdfdsdsfa",
          "selectedDropDown": "textBox",
          "qRequired": true,
          "options": [
            "options1",
            "options2"
          ]
        },
        {
          "qTitl": "asdfdasadsfdfas",
          "selectedDropDown": "checkBox",
          "qRequired": true,
          "options": [
            "options1",
            "options2",
            "option3",
            "option4"
          ]
        },
        {
          "qTitl": "asdfasdafssdfsdfadsdffadsasdfds",
          "selectedDropDown": "radio",
          "qRequired": true,
          "options": [
            "options1",
            "options2",
            "option3",
            "option4"
          ]
        }
      ],
      "createdBy": "test"
    },
    {
      "id": "3d1c",
      "AssignmentTitle": "tredfgasgd",
      "questions": [
        {
          "qTitl": "dsdfdsggds",
          "selectedDropDown": "textBox",
          "qRequired": true,
          "options": [
            "",
            ""
          ]
        },
        {
          "qTitl": "dfsgsdgd",
          "selectedDropDown": "radio",
          "qRequired": true,
          "options": [
            "dsfgdsdsg",
            "dsfdsdsgsdgdg"
          ]
        },
        {
          "qTitl": "dfsdsgdsdf",
          "selectedDropDown": "checkBox",
          "qRequired": true,
          "options": [
            "dgssdgdsdf",
            "ssdfgsddsgdsgdgsdsg"
          ]
        }
      ],
      "createdBy": "test"
    },
    {
      "id": "b1db",
      "AssignmentTitle": "alskdjlkfsadjlksfdajklsdajkljaksldj",
      "questions": [
        {
          "qTitl": ";lkjafsldkjfasdkljasdflkfsjksd",
          "selectedDropDown": "textBox",
          "qRequired": true,
          "options": [
            "",
            ""
          ]
        },
        {
          "qTitl": "dfnlsa;djksafdjisfd;jilafsjlsd",
          "selectedDropDown": "checkBox",
          "qRequired": true,
          "options": [
            "1",
            "2",
            "3",
            "4"
          ]
        },
        {
          "qTitl": "jasdfjkl;adsjilasfdjioaspdfjfasradio",
          "selectedDropDown": "radio",
          "qRequired": true,
          "options": [
            "1",
            "2",
            "3",
            "4"
          ]
        }
      ],
      "createdBy": "test"
    },
    {
      "id": "2fb1",
      "AssignmentTitle": "asdflksdjalfd",
      "questions": [
        {
          "qTitl": "asdflkjasdkfjsad",
          "selectedDropDown": "checkBox",
          "qRequired": false,
          "options": [
            "asdfasdasfdfsddsf",
            "HOw are you"
          ]
        }
      ],
      "createdBy": "test"
    }
  ],
  "responses": [
    {
      "id": "74e2",
      "quesAns": [
        {
          "question": "asdfdsasdfdsdsfa",
          "ans": "asdf;kjhsadklfjsalkdjsfdl"
        },
        {
          "question": "asdfdasadsfdfas",
          "ans": "option4"
        },
        {
          "question": "asdfasdafssdfsdfadsdffadsasdfds",
          "ans": "options2"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "8ccb",
      "assignmentTitle": "tredfgasgd",
      "quesAns": [
        {
          "question": "dsdfdsggds",
          "ans": "sadfljlsdkfjlisdjfklasdjilfjaslkdjfklasdjl"
        },
        {
          "question": "dfsgsdgd",
          "ans": "dsfdsdsgsdgdg"
        },
        {
          "question": "dfsdsgdsdf",
          "ans": "ssdfgsddsgdsgdgsdsg"
        }
      ],
      "assignmentId": "3d1c"
    },
    {
      "id": "7ae6",
      "assignmentTitle": "asdfasdasdffasd",
      "quesAns": [
        {
          "question": "asdfdsasdfdsdsfa"
        },
        {
          "question": "asdfdasadsfdfas"
        },
        {
          "question": "asdfasdafssdfsdfadsdffadsasdfds"
        }
      ],
      "assignmentId": "f9c5"
    },
    {
      "id": "c928",
      "assignmentTitle": "tredfgasgd",
      "quesAns": [
        {
          "question": "dsdfdsggds"
        },
        {
          "question": "dfsgsdgd"
        },
        {
          "question": "dfsdsgdsdf"
        }
      ],
      "assignmentId": "3d1c"
    },
    {
      "id": "768c",
      "assignmentTitle": "asdfasdasdffasd",
      "quesAns": [
        {
          "question": "asdfdsasdfdsdsfa"
        },
        {
          "question": "asdfdasadsfdfas"
        },
        {
          "question": "asdfasdafssdfsdfadsdffadsasdfds"
        }
      ],
      "assignmentId": "f9c5"
    },
    {
      "id": "5d1c",
      "assignmentTitle": "alskdjlkfsadjlksfdajklsdajkljaksldj",
      "quesAns": [
        {
          "question": ";lkjafsldkjfasdkljasdflkfsjksd",
          "ans": "asdfl'j;sldkajfklasdjlkfasdjdfasdl;fjaslksdjflkjads"
        },
        {
          "question": "dfnlsa;djksafdjisfd;jilafsjlsd",
          "ans": ""
        },
        {
          "question": "jasdfjkl;adsjilasfdjioaspdfjfasradio",
          "ans": "3"
        }
      ],
      "assignmentId": "b1db"
    },
    {
      "id": "af6e",
      "assignmentTitle": "asdfasdasdffasd",
      "quesAns": [
        {
          "question": "asdfdsasdfdsdsfa",
          "ans": "I am Shashank\n"
        },
        {
          "question": "asdfdasadsfdfas",
          "ans": "options1"
        },
        {
          "question": "asdfdasadsfdfas",
          "ans": "options1"
        },
        {
          "question": "asdfasdafssdfsdfadsdffadsasdfds"
        }
      ],
      "assignmentId": "f9c5"
    },
    {
      "id": "e518",
      "assignmentTitle": "asdfasdasdffasd",
      "quesAns": [
        {
          "question": "asdfdsasdfdsdsfa",
          "ans": "kxnvbcmhgjkghfnxvbn,jhkjghfncvbmjhgfcvbj,hgfcvbmjhgvbmjhgfcvbhjygfxcvbghjythdfxcvghjfdxcvbnhgfdxcvbnhjytfgdcvhgjyutrdfhjkliuytrefdsxcvgh gfhjuytgfcv ytgfhjuuyt ygvhjkiuygfvb utygfvhbjkliukyfjgcv buyjhvbk oiyftv ybuioft u7tyu o8kuo8ftvydrxcsetrserxt sexr t57dtyu gyut"
        },
        {
          "question": "asdfdasadsfdfas",
          "ans": "options2"
        },
        {
          "question": "asdfdsasdfdsdsfa",
          "ans": "kxnvbcmhgjkghfnxvbn,jhkjghfncvbmjhgfcvbj,hgfcvbmjhgvbmjhgfcvbhjygfxcvbghjythdfxcvghjfdxcvbnhgfdxcvbnhjytfgdcvhgjyutrdfhjkliuytrefdsxcvgh gfhjuytgfcv ytgfhjuuyt ygvhjkiuygfvb utygfvhbjkliukyfjgcv buyjhvbk oiyftv ybuioft u7tyu o8kuo8ftvydrxcsetrserxt sexr t57dtyu gyut"
        },
        {
          "question": "asdfdasadsfdfas",
          "ans": "options2"
        },
        {
          "question": "asdfdasadsfdfas",
          "ans": "option3"
        },
        {
          "question": "asdfasdafssdfsdfadsdffadsasdfds",
          "ans": "options2"
        }
      ],
      "assignmentId": "f9c5"
    },
    {
      "id": "9063",
      "assignmentTitle": "asdfasdasdffasd",
      "quesAns": [
        {
          "question": "asdfdsasdfdsdsfa"
        },
        {
          "question": "asdfdasadsfdfas"
        },
        {
          "question": "asdfasdafssdfsdfadsdffadsasdfds"
        }
      ],
      "assignmentId": "f9c5"
    },
    {
      "id": "4bbb",
      "assignmentTitle": "alskdjlkfsadjlksfdajklsdajkljaksldj",
      "quesAns": [
        {
          "question": ";lkjafsldkjfasdkljasdflkfsjksd",
          "ans": "admintesting\n"
        },
        {
          "question": "dfnlsa;djksafdjisfd;jilafsjlsd",
          "ans": "1, 2, 4"
        },
        {
          "question": "jasdfjkl;adsjilasfdjioaspdfjfasradio",
          "ans": "1"
        }
      ],
      "assignmentId": "b1db"
    },
    {
      "id": "4189",
      "assignmentTitle": "asdfasdasdffasd",
      "quesAns": [
        {
          "question": "asdfdsasdfdsdsfa",
          "ans": "dddddd"
        },
        {
          "question": "asdfdasadsfdfas",
          "ans": "options2, option4"
        },
        {
          "question": "asdfasdafssdfsdfadsdffadsasdfds",
          "ans": "option3"
        }
      ],
      "assignmentId": "f9c5"
    }
  ],
  "subQuestions": [
    {
      "id": "bab6"
    },
    {
      "id": "bdd6",
      "subQuestion1": "asdfadsfsfadasfd",
      "subQuestion2": "dddddd",
      "subQuestion3": "eeeeee"
    }
  ]
}